npf.gov.ng 2011-06-27

# Nigeria Police ForceTeam

| 

  *   *   

Minister of Police Affairs Humphrey Enemaku Abah in Force Headquarters Abuja

  * Former IGP Ogbonna O. Onovo handing over the security of Nigeria to IGP Hafiz Ringim  

  *   * The Nigeria Police Management Team  

  Privacy Policy 

|   | 

When you provide us with information through Nigeria Police Force Website (the "Site"), we respect your privacy. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information. Your visit to the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. Please note that this Privacy Policy governs only information provided to Nigeria Police Force Website and communications from Nigeria Police Force Website. It does not govern any other information or communications that may reference Nigeria Police Force Website. This Privacy Policy was last updated 22 June 2010.

1.      Collection of Personally Identifiable Information by Nigeria Police Force Website

> We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you decide to complete a user registration form or online survey, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number), age group, and gender. To protect your personal information, users registering at the Site may also be required to enter a user name/email address and password. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.
> 
> When you submit your personally identifiable information on the Site, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

2.      Use of Personally Identifiable Information by Nigeria Police Force Website

> a.     Opt-Out Communications
>
>> You may opt-out during the Site registration process or at other times when you submit personally identifiable information.  The information you provide may be used by Nigeria Police Force Website to create and deliver to you our newsletters, surveys or other communications containing product information, or promotions ("Communications"). If you prefer not to receive such Communications, please opt-out of receiving these communications. You may also opt-out by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any email communication you receive from us and following the instructions provided therein, or by emailing us at [info@npf.gov.ng](mailto:info@npf.gov.ng)
>> 
>> If you do opt-out and later decide that you would like to receive these communications, see Section 12 (Choice/Opt-In) below.
> 
> b.    Communications to Serve You
>
>> If you have elected to provide us with your contact information, e.g., by registering at the Site, emailing our Customer Service department or placing an order, we may provide you with service related announcements concerning the Site or contact you regarding your customer service requests or your order. For example, all registered users will receive a welcoming email to confirm their registration. These types of communications are necessary to serve you, respond to your concerns and to provide the high level of customer service that Nigeria Police Force Website offers. 

3.      No Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information for Third Party Marketing Without Your Consent

> We will never provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for their use in marketing their products or services to you without your consent. 

4.      Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information

> a.     Fraud Protection and Compliance with Law
>
>> We may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.
> 
> b.    Service Providers
>
>> We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions consistent with our Privacy Policy on our behalf. Examples include customer support specialists, web hosting companies, fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings), data analysis firms and email service providers. Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. 
> 
> c.     Special Events
>
>> If you elect to participate in any promotions, sweepstakes, surveys, questionnaires or other events during your visit to our Site, the rules or terms and conditions for those events may indicate that your personally identifiable information will be shared with third parties. By choosing to participate and submitting your personally identifiable information with respect to such events, you consent to disclosure of your personally identifiable information to such third parties. 
> 
> d.    Business Transfers
>
>> As we continue to develop our business, we might sell certain of our assets. In such transactions, user information, including personally identifiable information, generally is one of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your personal information on the Site you agree that your data may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances.

5.      Cookies and IP Addresses

> We may place a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive so we can recognize you as a return user and personalize your experience. A cookie is a piece of data that enables us to track and target your preferences. The cookie will be stored on your computer's hard drive until you remove it. We may also use temporary or "session" cookies to help you shop. These cookies will expire when you place an order. You can have your browser notify you of, or automatically reject, cookies. If you reject our cookies, you may still use the Site, but you may be limited in the use of some of the features. Some of our business partners may also use cookies on the Site. However, we have no access to, or control over, these cookies and do not accept any responsibility for such use. In addition, we may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track traffic patterns, and gather demographic information for aggregate use, as well as in combination with your personally identifiable information for credit fraud protection and risk reduction. 

6.      Pixel Tags and Tracking Technology

> When you visit this Site or view one of our emails, we may use pixel tags (also called "clear" gifs), tracking links and/or similar technology to note some of the pages you visit on our Site and personalize your experience. We may also use pixel tags to determine what types of email your browser supports. We may use the information collected through pixel tags, tracking links and similar technology in combination with your personally identifiable information.

7.      Use of Aggregate Information

> We may use the information you provide in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of the Site, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular. We may share or transfer non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners.

8.      Supervision of Minors and Children's Online Privacy Protection Act

> We cannot prohibit minors from visiting the Site. We must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervising children under 18 to decide which materials are appropriate for such children to view and/or purchase.
> 
> In accordance to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we take special steps to safeguard the privacy pf children. If you are under 13 years of age, you may browse our Site. However, you may not provide personal information to us. For example, you cannot register or make a purchase. This Site is not designed for children and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any children under 13. 

9.      Links

> The Site may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites including, without limitation, Gloss.com. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on the Site. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from the Site or otherwise visit.

10.     Security

> We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our web site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. InfiniteAloe.com's servers use an encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, and AOL's browser, so that only npf.gov.ng can read a customer's personal information.
> 
> In addition, we implement various security measures in accordance with industry standards to protect the security of your personal information both online and offline. If you have any questions about security at the Site, you can email us by [clicking here](mailto:info@npf.gov.ng).

11.     Notification of Changes

> We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Please note that our rights to use your personally identifiable information will be based on the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is used.

12.     Choice/Opt-In

> If you have elected to opt-out of receiving communications from Nigeria Police Force Website when you registered at the Site or clicked the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any email you received from InfiniteAloe and following the instructions provided therein, or by emailing us, you may change your preferences at any time by revising your profile by [clicking here](mailto:Info@npf.gov.ng).

13.     Legal disclaimer

> In accordance to our Terms and Conditions, this Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control. This Privacy Policy is governed by Nigeria law, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in Nigeria within one year after the claim arose, or be barred.

14.     Comments

> We have taken great measures to ensure that your visit to the Site is an excellent one and that your privacy is constantly respected. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about the Site's privacy practices, please contact us by email at [legal@npf.gov.ng](mailto:legal@npf.gov.ng).

Copyright© 2010 Nigeria Police Force. All worldwide rights reserved.  
  
---|---  
  
Abia State Command 08035415408, Adamawa STATE COMMAND 08089671313, Akwa Ibom STATE COMMAND 08182951257, Anambra STATE COMMAND 07034578208, Bauchi STATE COMMAND 08125274185, Bayelsa STATE COMMAND 07034578208, Benue STATE COMMAND 08053039936,08066006475, 08080792550, BORNO STATE COMMAND 08036071667, 08123823322, CROSS RIVER STATE COMMAND 08133568456, 07053355415, 07029107411, DELTA STATE COMMAND 08036684974, EBONYI STATE COMMAND 07064950600, EDO STATE COMMAND 08038156615, EKITI STATE COMMAND 08081768750, ENUGU STATE 08032003702, GOMBE STATE COMMAND 08132196764, IMO STATE COMMAND 08033424051, JIGAWA STATE COMMAND 08123821598, KADUNA STATE COMMAND 08123822284 KANO STATE COMMAND 064977004, 064977005, KASTINA STATE COMMAND 08065581244 KEBBI STATE COMMAND 08081161283, 08187175282, KOGI STATE COMMAND 08126375838, 08038329084, 07087233230, KWARA STATE COMMAND 08125275046, LAGOS STATE COMMAND 07055462708, NASARAWA STATE COMMAND 08125275046, NIGER STATE COMMAND, 08081777593, 08081777496ONDO STATE COMMAND 07034313903, OGUN STATE COMMAND 08032136765, 08081770416, OSUN STATE COMMAND, 08036491684, OYOY STATE COMMAND, 08081768614, 08034029268 PLATEAU STATE COMMAND, 08038907662, 08050375280, RIVERS STATE COMMAND, 08073777717, 08032003514, SOKOTO STATE COMMAND, 08023563420, TARABA STATE COMMAND, 08081772288, YOBE STATE COMMAND, 08037034711, ZAMFARA STATE COMMAND, 08036186543, FCT COMMAND 08061881938, 08032003913, 07029311600, 07057337653
